Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
Shall we take Elias' daughter?
The cells are packed solid. aren't they?
What do you think of my new ship?
Who are you?
What did you hit now. Lloyd?
The watch.
She's flying towards the sun!
We've lost our engines!
Found them.
Let her have him.
Krem has the strength of one thousand men.
He'll tear this little girl apart.
Sorry. we are a bit backed up.
Have you seen him?
Is it now? I thought we had more time.
So did I.
but Krypton's core is too unstable.
It will explode in minutes.
I have triggered the force field.
We need to go.
Alura!
Now!
Is that him?
That is Kal-El.
The sweet little boy your brother has
declared a conqueror of worlds.
It's time.
Are we fools. Zor-El?
Should we have listened to your brother?
We can't send our daughter...
to another planet to be some sort of god.
We preserved all this for a reason.
We have to believe there's a future here.
Kara. where are you?
Tell me.
When Argo City broke off. it unearthed...
a crystalline mineral
buried deep in the planet.
Kryptonite.
The soil has been poisoned.
People are ill all over Argo...
and it's spreading.
And can it be helped?
Kara.
What is all this?
Trying to preserve Argo
with my force field was a failure.
The radiation has taken hold of me. too.
I cannot let it get you.
I found my brother's sketches
for the escape pod.
I made it big enough for you.
You will follow your cousin. Kal-El.
You will make a new home on Earth.
No!
This is my home.
This is my only home.
Let the radiation take me too.
I'll lie in the ground next to you
and next to mom.
I am one tiny life.
What difference does it make
whether I live or die?
You are not one tiny life.
You are your mother's life.
You are my life.
You are our souls unfolding
into the future.
My child...
this is why you must live.
When I am gone.
I need you to promise me something.
Of course. mother.
Just be good.
That doesn't mean you cannot be tough.
And that doesn't mean you have to be nice.
But you must be good.
We do not choose our paths.
Your path will be one of great effort...
of great purpose.
Where you are going.
you will have enormous power.
Use it to protect those...
who cannot protect themselves.
Trust yourself...
to know what is right. Kara.
We are with you.
Bomar. stop! It's for our daughter.
we have no choice.
Bring me their daughter.
Now.
The brides!
Get them! Get them!
A deal is a deal.
She has to die.
I don't understand you.
Where am I?
Is this Earth?
Are you Kal-El?
Krypto. be good. buddy.
Be good.
Why is he in his underwear?
How can this be home?
A dead Kryptonian...
should make for a magnificent trophy.
I'm working on it.
Get off your fat ass...
and take her to Krem.
He'll shut her up.
Keep your trap shut and do as you're told.
Where you are going.
you will have enormous power.
I need you to promise me something.
Use it to protect those...
who cannot protect themselves.
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm